[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie St. Elmos Fire, when Leslie is packing up at her and Alecs old place, Alec tells her that music by what artist is not leaving?", "correct_answer": "Bruce Springsteen", "incorrect_answers": ["Moliere", "Carly Simon", "The Police"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following artists does not produce trance music?", "correct_answer": "Van Morrison", "incorrect_answers": ["Delirium", "Paul van Dyk", "Tito"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What iconic world landmark, sometimes called the Crossroads of the World, was formerly named Longacre Square?", "correct_answer": "Times Square", "incorrect_answers": ["Grosvenor Square", "Madison Square", "St Jamess Square"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "I wasnt speaking to you Mr. Krendler. When I speak to you, youll know it because Ill look at you is a line taken from which film?", "correct_answer": "Hannibal", "incorrect_answers": ["The Silence of the Lambs", "The Red Dragon", "Seven"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During  first quarter moon, what time does the moon rise?", "correct_answer": "noon", "incorrect_answers": ["dawn", "midnight", "sunset"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Return of the Jedi, Luke severs one of Darth Vaders body parts in a lightsaber fight.  What part does Vader lose?", "correct_answer": "Right Hand", "incorrect_answers": ["Left leg", "Left Hand", "Right Leg"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Does Mercury have an atmosphere?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first Broadway comedy to run for over 5500 performances?", "correct_answer": "Oh! Calcutta", "incorrect_answers": ["Grease", "Hello Dolly", "Drat, the Cat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the first in-flight magazine for commercial flights?", "correct_answer": "Clipper", "incorrect_answers": ["Air News", "Pan American News", "Traveller"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What famous scientist discovered Jupiters four largest satellites?", "correct_answer": "Galileo Galilei", "incorrect_answers": ["Giovanni Cassini", "Johannes Kepler", "Robert Hooke"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The medical prefix bucco refers to which part of the head?", "correct_answer": "Cheek", "incorrect_answers": ["Forehead", "Eye", "Nose"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Does gasoline float on distilled water?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}]